Guide to the Organization for Tropical Studies Records, 1962 - 1974 UA.26.03.0029
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Courses, 1962-1974
  - #72-4: Geography, 1971-1972 (July-August 1972 session) (Box 7, Folder 267)
  - #74-1: Tropical Biology, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 268)
  - #75-1: Tropical Biology, 1974 (January-February 1975 session) (Box 7, Folder 269)
  - Critiques
    - 1971 (Box 7, Folder 270)
    - Biology, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 271)
    - Forestry, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Folder 272)
    - Fundamentals, 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 273)
    - Fundamentals, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 274)
  - Planning
    - 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 275)
    - 1969 (Box 7, Folder 276)
    - 1969-1970, for 1971 courses (Box 7, Folder 277)
    - Advanced Biology, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 278)
    - Agriculture, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 279)
    - Geography, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 280)
    - Meteorology, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 281)
    - Tropical Biology: An Ecological Approach, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 282)
  - Related Information
    - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 283)
    - Correspondence on 1970 courses, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 284)
    - Course Information, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 285)
    - Fundamentals Course - Spanish, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 286)
    - Insurance for Participants, 1968-1969, undated (Box 7, Folder 287)
    - OTS Curriculum, 1962-1967 (Box 7, Folder 288)
    - OTS Faculty, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 289)
    - Policy Statement for Instructors (Instructors' Manual), 1965-1968 (Box 7, Folder 290)
    - Summer Course Information
      - 1965 (Box 7, Folder 291)
      - 1967 (Box 7, Folder 292)
      - 1968 (Box 7, Folder 293)